export const questions = [
  {
    question: "Sublingual administration means under the:",
    options: ['Skin', 'Tongue', 'Muscle', 'Vein'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Intramuscular injection is given into:",
    options: ['Muscle', 'Vein', 'Artery', 'Bone'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Drug movement from blood to tissues is called:",
    options: ['Absorption', 'Distribution', 'Elimination', 'Filtration'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Chloroprocaine is an example of:",
    options: ['Amide', 'Ester', 'Opioid', 'Steroid'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Mepivacaine belongs to:",
    options: ['Amides', 'Esters', 'Opioids', 'Barbiturates'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Central regional anesthesia affects the:",
    options: ['Heart', 'Spinal cord', 'Liver', 'Kidney'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Desflurane is a type of:",
    options: ['IV opioid', 'Inhalation anesthetic', 'Antibiotic', 'Muscle relaxant'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Seroflurane is administered by:",
    options: ['Oral', 'IV', 'Inhalation', 'Subcutaneous'],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Morphine IV is mainly for:",
    options: ['Analgesia', 'Muscle relaxation', 'Antibiotic', 'Sedation only'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Benzodiazepines IV produce:",
    options: ['Unconsciousness', 'Muscle paralysis', 'Antibiotic effect', 'Diuresis'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Preoperative evaluation includes previous:",
    options: ['Travel history', 'Anesthesia history', 'School grades', 'Diet plan'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Cardiac function should be checked before:",
    options: ['Anesthesia', 'Sleeping', 'Eating', 'Walking'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "IV fluids are given during:",
    options: ['Operation', 'Driving', 'Sleeping', 'Exercise'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Reflex monitoring is done:",
    options: ['During operation', 'After discharge', 'At home', 'In gym'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "General anesthesia includes muscle:",
    options: ['Growth', 'Relaxation', 'Pain', 'Infection'],
    answer: 1
  },
];